{"data":[{"question":"The fact that half of the known species is thought to inhabit the world's rain forests does not seem surprising, considering the huge numbers of insects that comprise the bulk of the species.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"among ","b":"of the space","c":"is reserved ","d":"advertising","answer":"1","explain":"- Among-> about","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Many of the recording instruments used in vary branches of science are kymographs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sets ","b":"apart from ","c":"much of ","d":"go on ","answer":"4","explain":"- Go on->goes on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"In the United States among 60 percent of the space on the pages of newspapers is reserved for advertising.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"plant ","b":"been extinct ","c":"fifty million years ","d":"near ","answer":"1","explain":"- Plant-> plants","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The spontaneity of children's artwork sets it apart from the regulated uniforming of much of what otherwise go on in traditional extraordinary classrooms.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"timberland ","b":"is classed ","c":"temperate","d":"rain forests","answer":"4","explain":"- Rain forests-> rain forest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Fossils of plant that have been extinct for fifty million years have been found in large deposits of amber near the Baltic Sea.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"found ","b":"indicate ","c":"clothes ","d":"years ago","answer":"4","explain":"- Years ago-> years before","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The luxuriant hardwood timberland of the southern Appalachian Mountains is classed as a temperate rain forests.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to have been formed ","b":"when ","c":"already ","d":"years","answer":"4","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Bone and ivory needles found at archaeological sites indicate that clothes have been sewn for some 17,000 years ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"frequently ","b":"and ","c":"as ","d":"passing ","answer":"4","explain":"-Passing->pass","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The sun seems to have been formed when the universe was already 10 billion years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Though ","b":"only slight ","c":"another","d":"he became ","answer":"3","explain":"- Another-> other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The satellites are frequently eclipsed by Jupiter and may be seen to transit Jupiter as dark shadows or passing behind the planet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"chief executive ","b":"two full terms ","c":"leave ","d":"in his ears","answer":"3","explain":"- Leave->left","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Though Artist Tatun was totally blind in one eye and had only slight vision in another, he became an internationally renowned jazz musician.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"discriminating ","b":"that ","c":"good ","d":"as any ","answer":"4","explain":"-As any-> as ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}